//This contains the questions
var questionArray = [{
    question: "What color is santas clothes?",
    answer: "Correct! They are red & white!",
    options: ["Blue & black", "Red & white", "None, he's naked"],
    answerID: "A2"
}, {
    question: "Which is one of santas reindeers?",
    answer: "Correct! Dasher runs first followed by Dancer, Prancer, Vixen, Comet, Cupid, Donner, Blitzen",
    options: ["Flasher", "Smasher", "Dasher"],
    answerID: "A3"
}, {
    question: "Do you like cookies?",
    answer: "Correct! omnomnom",
    options: ["Yes", "No", "Dont know"],
    answerID: "A1"
},
{
    question: "Which color is yellow snow?",
    answer: "That is correct!",
    options: ["Yellow", "White", "Red"],
    answerID: "A1"
},
{
    question: "Why doesn't Santa have any children?",
    answer: "That is right! He only comes once a year, and when he does, it's down the chimney",
    options: ["He doesn't want to", "No one knows", "He only comes once a year"],
    answerID: "A3"
},
{
    question: "Where does Santa put your presents?",
    answer: "Yes, of course it is under the tree, unless you have been naughty.",
    options: ["Under the bed", "Under the tree", "In the trash"],
    answerID: "A2"
},
{
    question: "How do you make the best snowballs?",
    answer: "Yes you're right! Even better would be to use yellow snow.",
    options: ["Squeeze them really hard", "Squeeze them hard and then dip them in water and squeeze again", "Do not squeeze them"],
    answerID: "A2"
},
{
    question: "What does Santa say?",
    answer: "Yes, of course he says ho ho ho",
    options: ["Ho ho ho", "Hoe hoe hoe", "No no no"],
    answerID: "A1"
},
{
    question: "What do you put on roads to prevent cars from slipping in the winter?",
    answer: "Correct! The other two would not be very good.",
    options: ["Salt", "Water", "Kittens"],
    answerID: "A1"
},
{
    question: "What element has the lowest freezing point?",
    answer: "You are correct! Helium has the lowest freezing point at -272Â°C",
    options: ["Liquid nitrogen", "Plutonium", "Helium"],
    answerID: "A3"
},
{
    question: "Nananananananana",
    answer: "Array(16).join( 'hero'-1) + 'Batman';",
    options: ["Batman", "Superman", "Kittens"],
    answerID: "A1"
},
{
    question: "Which is NOT a real web browser",
    answer: "Array(16).join( 'hero'-1) + 'Batman';",
    options: ["Opera", "Firefox", "Internet Explorer"],
    answerID: "A3"
}];

module.exports = questionArray;
